Washingtoniana Vertical File Index VF.001 VF.001
Test
- Diseases. Yellow Fever
- Displays and exhibits SEE Business, Individual. Displays and exhibits
- Dissection
- District Building (by date) SEE ALSO Buildings. Office. D.C. Government; Municipal Center
- District Employees (by date)
- District Employees. Center for Excellence in Municipal Management
- District Employees. Furlough
- District Employees. Legislation
- District Employees. One Fund Drive Directories
- District Employees. Pamphlets
- District Employees. Political Activity
- District Employees. Residency Requirements
- District Employees. Retirement (by date)
- District Employees. Salaries (by date)
- District Employees. Saturday Half Holiday
- District Employees. Scandals
- District Employees. Strikes
- District Grocery Stores SEE Stores. District Grocery Stores
- District Internal Audit Office SEE Internal Audit Office
- District of Columbia Bar SEE ALSO Law and Lawyers
- District Personnel Board
- District Property Yards
- District Repair Shop
- District Village SEE Old Age. Old Age Homes. Home for the Aged and Infirm. "District Village"
- Divers SEE Business, Individual. Divers
- Diversity SEE Public Schools. Diversity
- Division of Printing and Publications SEE Printing and Publications, Division of
- Divorce SEE Marriage and Divorce
- Documents, Office of
- Dogs (by date) SEE ALSO Animals
- Dogs. Army Canine Corps.
- Dolls (by date)
- Domestic Abuse SEE Crime and Criminals. Specific Cases. Domestic Abuse; Women. Abused
- Domestic Relations Court (Family Court) SEE Courts. Domestic Relations Court
- Domestics SEE Business, Individual. Domestics
- Domicile
- Dominican House of Studies SEE Colleges and Universities. Dominican House of Studies
- Doorways
- Doris Hat Stores SEE Stores. Doris Hat Stores
- Downtown (by date) SEE ALSO Residential Sections. Downtown
- Downtown. Downtown Washington: A Walking Guide
- Downtown. Interactive Downtown D.C. Task Force
- Downtown. Pamphlets SEE ALSO Residential Sections. Downtown. Pamphlets
- Downtown. Progress Reports (by date) SEE ALSO City Planning
- Draft Boards SEE Military Training. Compulsory. Draft Boards
- Drama (by date) SEE ALSO Community Center. Dramatic Activities; Drama Clubs; Moving Pictures; Theaters
- Drama Clubs
- Drama Clubs. A-C
- Drama Clubs. A-C. Children's Theater of Washington
- Drama Clubs. A-C. Cross Roads Theater
- Drama Clubs. D-E
- Drama Clubs. D-E. Drama Guild of Washington
- Drama Clubs. D-E. Drama League of America
- Drama Clubs. F-G
- Drama Clubs. H-M
- Drama Clubs. H-M. Lyric Theater
- Drama Clubs. H-M. Market Playhouse
- Drama Clubs. H-M. Mount Vernon Players
- Drama Clubs. H-M. Municipal Theater (proposed)
- Drama Clubs. N-Z
- Drama Clubs. N-Z. National Civic Theater Society
- Drama Clubs. N-Z. Negro
- Drama Clubs. N-Z. Pierce Hall Players
- Drama Clubs. N-Z. Ram's Head Players
- Drama Clubs. N-Z. St. Patrick's Players
- Drama Clubs. N-Z. Theater Lobby
- Drama Clubs. N-Z. Washington Civic Theater (by date)
- Drama, History of
- Dramatic Activities SEE Community Center. Dramatic Activities
- Dress designing and making SEE Business, Individual. Dress designing and making
- Driving While Intoxicated SEE Automobiles. Driving While Intoxicated
- Dropouts SEE Public Schools. Dropouts
- Drug Use SEE Politics and Government. Drug Use
- Drugs, Illegal SEE ALSO Crime and Criminals. Specific Cases. Drugs; Narcotics
- Drugfair SEE Stores. Drugstores. Drugfair
- Druggist SEE Business, Individual. Druggist
- Drugstores SEE Stores. Drugstores
- Dry cleaning SEE Business, Individual. Dry Cleaning
- Dry goods SEE Business, Individual. Dry goods
- Duels
- Duels. Decatur-Barron SEE ALSO Bladensburg
- Duels. Separate Duels 1822-1934
- Dumbarton Oaks SEE Parks. Dumbarton Oaks
- Dunbarton College of the Holy Cross SEE Colleges and Universities. Dunbarton College
- Dupont Circle SEE Circles and Squares. Dupont Circle; Houses. Dupont Circle; Residential Sections. Dupont Circle
- Early Childhood Development, Office of
- Earthquakes.
- East Potomac Park SEE Parks. East Potomac
- East Washington Railway (formerly Chesapeake Beach) SEE Railroads. East Washington Railway
- Easter SEE Days, Special. Easter
- Eastern Market SEE Markets. Eastern
- Eastland SEE Residential Sections. Eastland
- Ebenezer (Sq. 1102) SEE Cemeteries. Ebenezer (Sq. 1102)
- Eccentric Characters SEE Biography, collective. Eccentric characters
- Eclipses
- Ecology
- Economic Conditions SEE ALSO Description (by date); Statistics
- Economic Development, Dept. of (created March 1969 combining Occupations And Professional Depts.)
- Edgewood SEE Residential Sections. Edgewood
- Education SEE ALSO Adult Education; College and Universities; Schools
- Education, Board of (by date)
- Education, Board of. Community Grams and Action Sheets
- Education, Board of. Elections
- Education, Board of. Legislation
- Education, Board of. Subcommittee on Special Education
- Education, Board of. Union Agreement
- Edward R. Murrow Park SEE Parks. Edward R. Murrow Park (Reservation 31 -- 18th and H and Pennsylvania Ave)
- EEO Committee SEE Public Library. EEO Committee
- Eisenhower Funeral SEE Funerals. Eisenhower
- Eisenhower Theater SEE John F. Kennedy Center. Eisenhower Theater
- El Pueblo SEE Newspapers. El Pueblo
- Elections and Ethics, D.C. Board of
- Elections and Voting SEE Politics and government. Elections and Voting
- Elections. Rules and Regulations
- Electricity. 1887-
- Electricity. Electronics
- Electricity. Pepco
- Electricity. Pepco. Pamphlets
- Electronic appliances SEE Business, Individual. Electronic appliances
- Electronic equipment SEE Business, Individual. Electronic equipment
- Elesavetgrad Cemetery SEE Cemeteries. Elesavetgrad (Hebrew)
- Elevator operators SEE Business, Individual. Elevator operators
- Elevators SEE Building Elevators and Elevator Regulations
- Ellipse Fountain SEE Fountains. Ellipse
- Ellipse SEE Parks. Ellipse
- Elm Tree SEE Trees. Elm
- Emancipation, Centennial Committee
- Embassies and legations (by date)
- Embassies and legations (by country)
- Embassies and legations. Afghanistan
- Embassies and legations. Albania
- Embassies and legations. Algeria
- Embassies and legations. American Indian-Mexican
- Embassies and legations. Angola
- Embassies and legations. Argentina
- Embassies and legations. Australia
- Embassies and legations. Austria
- Embassies and legations. Bangladesh
- Embassies and legations. Belgium
- Embassies and legations. Benin
- Embassies and legations. Bolivia (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Botswana
- Embassies and legations. Brazil (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Brunei
- Embassies and legations. Bulgaria
- Embassies and legations. Burma
- Embassies and legations. Burundi, Kingdom of
- Embassies and legations. Cambodia
- Embassies and legations. Cameroon
- Embassies and legations. Canada
- Embassies and legations. Ceylon
- Embassies and legations. Chancery Row
- Embassies and legations. Children
- Embassies and legations. Chile
- Embassies and legations. China (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Christian Embassy
- Embassies and legations. Colombia (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Congo
- Embassies and legations. Costa Rica
- Embassies and legations. Cuba (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Cyprus
- Embassies and legations. Czechoslovakia (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Dahomey
- Embassies and legations. Denmark
- Embassies and legations. Dominican Republic
- Embassies and legations. East Germany
- Embassies and legations. Ecuador (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Egypt
- Embassies and legations. El Salvador
- Embassies and legations. Estonia
- Embassies and legations. Ethiopia
- Embassies and legations. Finland (by date)
- Embassies and legations. France (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Gabon
- Embassies and legations. Gambia
- Embassies and legations. Georgia
- Embassies and legations. Germany
- Embassies and legations. Ghana (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Great Britain (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Greek
- Embassies and legations. Guatemala
- Embassies and legations. Guinea
- Embassies and legations. Guyana
- Embassies and legations. Haiti
- Embassies and legations. Honduras
- Embassies and legations. Hungary
- Embassies and legations. Iceland
- Embassies and legations. Immunity (by date)
- Embassies and legations. India (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Indonesia
- Embassies and legations. International Center for the National Capital
- Embassies and legations. Iran (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Iraq
- Embassies and legations. Ireland, Republic of
- Embassies and legations. Israel
- Embassies and legations. Italy (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Ivory Coast
- Embassies and legations. Jamaica
- Embassies and legations. Japan (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Jordan
- Embassies and legations. Kenya
- Embassies and legations. Korea
- Embassies and legations. Kuwait
- Embassies and legations. Laos
- Embassies and legations. Latvia
- Embassies and legations. Lebanon
- Embassies and legations. Lesotho (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Liaison
- Embassies and legations. Liberia (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Libya
- Embassies and legations. Lithuania (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Luxembourg
- Embassies and legations. Malagasy Republic (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Malawi
- Embassies and legations. Malaya
- Embassies and legations. Mali (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Mauritania
- Embassies and legations. Mexico
- Embassies and legations. Morocco
- Embassies and legations. Nepal
- Embassies and legations. Netherlands (by date)
- Embassies and legations. New Zealand (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Nicaragua (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Niger
- Embassies and legations. Nigeria (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Norway (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Oman
- Embassies and legations. Pakistan
- Embassies and legations. Pamphlets
- Embassies and legations. Panama (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Papua New Guinea
- Embassies and legations. Paraguay
- Embassies and legations. Peru
- Embassies and legations. Philippines
- Embassies and legations. Poland (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Portugal (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Qatar
- Embassies and legations. Rhodesia (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Romania (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Russia (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Rwanda
- Embassies and legations. St. Vincent and Grenadine
- Embassies and legations. Saudi Arabia
- Embassies and legations. Senegal (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Sierra Leone
- Embassies and legations. Solomon Islands
- Embassies and legations. Somalia
- Embassies and legations. South Africa (by date) SEE ALSO Picketing, Protest, Demonstrations. South African Embassy, 1984
- Embassies and legations. South Vietnam SEE ALSO Embassies and legations. Vietnam
- Embassies and legations. Soviet Union SEE Embassies and legations. Russia
- Embassies and legations. Spain (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Sudan (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Sweden (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Switzerland (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Syria
- Embassies and legations. Taiwan
- Embassies and legations. Tajikistan
- Embassies and legations. Thailand (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Togo
- Embassies and legations. Tours
- Embassies and legations. Transjordan
- Embassies and legations. Tunisia
- Embassies and legations. Turkey
- Embassies and legations. Uganda
- Embassies and legations. United Arab Republic (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Upper Volta (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Uruguay
- Embassies and legations. Vatican City
- Embassies and legations. Venezuela
- Embassies and legations. Vietnam SEE ALSO Embassies and legations. South Vietnam
- Embassies and legations. Yemen
- Embassies and legations. Yugoslavia (by date)
- Embassies and legations. Zambia (by date)
- Emergency Management Agency
- Emergency Medical Services SEE ALSO Ambulances
- Emergency Preparedness
- Emergency Storage SEE Defense. Emergency Storage
- Emergency Telephone Service (911)
- Eminent Domain SEE ALSO Land Condemnation; Residential Sections. Southwest
- Employee Appeals, Office of
- Employee Relations Committee SEE Public Library. Employee Relations Committee
- Employers' Liability (by date)
- Employers' Liability. Pamphlets
- Employment (by date) SEE ALSO Unemployment
- Employment. CETA (includes Manpower Services Planning Advisory Council Report)
- Employment. Discrimination
- Employment. Legislation
- Employment. Pamphlets (by date)
- Employment. Security Building
- Employment Agencies SEE ALSO Business, Individual. Employment Agencies
- Employment Services, D.C. Department of SEE ALSO previous agencies: Labor Department, D.C.; Manpower, D.C. Department of)
- Energy
- Energy Office, D.C. SEE ALSO Federal Energy Office
- Engineer Department
- Engineering SEE ALSO Business, Individual. Engineering
- Engineering. Board of Registration for Profession Engineers
- Engineers, U.S. Corps of
- Engraving and Printing, Bureau of
- Engraving and Printing, Bureau of. Annex
- Engraving SEE Business, Individual. Engraving.
- Enrollment SEE Public Schools. Enrollment
- Entertainment SEE Business, Individual. Entertainment
- Entrepreneurs
- Environmental Service Corps
- Environmental Services, Department of (by date)
- Episcopal Home for Children SEE Children's Homes. Episcopal Center for Children
- Escort services SEE Business, Individual. Escort services
- Espionage SEE Crime and Criminals. Specific Cases. Espionage
- Ethic Groups
- Ethnic Groups. Afghan
- Ethnic Groups. African
- Ethnic Groups. American Indians SEE Indians
- Ethnic Groups. Arabs
- Ethnic Groups. Armenian
- Ethnic Groups. Asian
- Ethnic Groups. Bangladeshi
- Ethnic Groups. Bosnian
- Ethnic Groups. Brazilian
- Ethnic Groups. Burmese
- Ethnic Groups. Cambodian SEE Ethnic Groups. Indochinese
- Ethnic Groups. Chilean
- Ethnic Groups. Chinese (by date)
- Ethnic Groups. Cuban
- Ethnic Groups. Czechoslovakian
- Ethnic Groups. Dane
- Ethnic Groups. Druze
- Ethnic Groups. Egyptian
- Ethnic Groups. English
- Ethnic Groups. Ethiopian
- Ethnic Groups. Filipino
- Ethnic Groups. French
- Ethnic Groups. German
- Ethnic Groups. Greek
- Ethnic Groups. Guyanese
- Ethnic Groups. Gypsies
- Ethnic Groups. Haitian
- Ethnic Groups. Hispanic (by date) SEE ALSO Ethnic Groups. Latino
- Ethnic Groups. Hispanic. Pamphlets
- Ethnic Groups. Honduran
- Ethnic Groups. Hungarian
- Ethnic Groups. Immigrants (by date)
- Ethnic Groups. Indian (India)
- Ethnic Groups. Indochinese
- Ethnic Groups. Iranian
- Ethnic Groups. Iraqi
- Ethnic Groups. Irish
- Ethnic Groups. Israelis
- Ethnic Groups. Italian
- Ethnic Groups. Jamaican
- Ethnic Groups. Japanese
- Ethnic Groups. K (includes Koreans)
- Ethnic Groups. Latinos SEE ALSO Ethnic Groups. Hispanic
- Ethnic Groups. Liberian
- Ethnic Groups. Mexican
- Ethnic Groups. Nigerian
- Ethnic Groups. Palestinian
- Ethnic Groups. Peruvian
- Ethnic Groups. Polish
- Ethnic Groups. Russian
- Ethnic Groups. Salvadoran
- Ethnic Groups. Scottish
- Ethnic Groups. Serbs
- Ethnic Groups. Somalian
- Ethnic Groups. South African
- Ethnic Groups. Swedish
- Ethnic Groups. Swiss
- Ethnic Groups. Thai
- Ethnic Groups. Ukrainian
- Ethnic Groups. Venezuelan
- Ethnic Groups. Vietnamese
- Ethnic Groups. Welsh
- Etiquette SEE Social Life
- European War 1914-1918 SEE World War I
- European War 1939-1945 SEE World War II
- Evening Express SEE Newspapers. Evening Express
- Evening Star SEE Newspapers. Evening Star
- Evergreen Trees SEE Trees. Evergreen
- Evictions
- Excise Board
- Executive Office Building SEE State, War, and Navy Building
- Executive Protection Service
- Exercise
- Exhibitions (by date) SEE ALSO Art. A-Z. Exhibits and Organizations
- Exhibitions. Panoramas
- Exorcism
- Exorcist SEE Moving Pictures. Washington locale. The Exorcist
- Expenditures, Public SEE Finance. Appropriations
- Export-Import Business SEE Foreign Trade
- Extension Program SEE Public Library. Extension Program
- Exterminators SEE Business, Individual. Exterminating Service
- Eyeglasses and artificial eyes SEE Business, Individual. Eyeglasses, Contact lens and artificial eyes
- Fairfax County SEE Metropolitan District. Virginia. Fairfax County
- Fairlawn SEE Residential Sections. Fairlawn
- Fairs (by date)
- Fairs. World's (Chicago, New York, San Francisco)
- Faith Healing SEE Spiritualism
- Families (includes Household information)
- Family Abandonment SEE Abandonment of Family
- Family and Child Services Agency
- Family and Child Services of Washington (by date)
- Family Rehabilitation. Storage Center
- Famous Fires SEE Fires. Famous
- Fannie Mae Candy SEE Stores. Fannie Mae Candy
- Fantles Drugstore SEE Stores. Drugstores. Fantles
- Fares and farecards SEE Subways. Fares and farecards
- Fares SEE Buses. Fares
- Farmers Markets SEE Markets. Farmers
- Farms and Farming SEE ALSO Animals
- Farragut Square SEE Circles and Squares. Farragut Square
- Fashion Shows
- Fashions SEE ALSO Clothing and Dress
- Fauna and Flora (by date) SEE ALSO Animals
- FBI Building SEE Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) Building
- FDIC Building SEE Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation Building
- Federal Aviation Agency (FAA) Building
- Federal Bake Shop SEE Stores. Federal Bake Shop
- Federal Budget Cuts SEE Finances. Federal Budget Cuts
- Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) Building (by date)
- Federal City College SEE Colleges and Universities. Federal City College
- Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC) Building
- Federal Employees (by date)
- Federal Employees. Government Girl Campaign
- Federal Employees. "Jane's Journal" 1942
- Federal Enclave SEE Politics and government. Federal enclave
- Federal Energy Office
- Federal News SEE Newspapers. Federal News
- Federal Payment SEE ALSO Finances. Budget; Finances. Fiscal Relations
- Federal Protective Service
- Federal Reserve Building
- Federal Trade Commission (FTC) Building
- Federal Trade Commission. Consumer Complaint Office
- Federal Triangle SEE Triangle (Federal Triangle)
- Federation of Citizens' Associations (by date)
- Federation of Citizens' Associations. Citizens Advisory Council
- Federation of Citizens' Associations. Constitution and Bylaws
- Federation of Citizens' Associations. History
- Federation of Citizens' Associations. List of Affiliated Bodies
- Federation of Citizens' Associations SEE ALSO Civic Associations, Federation of
- Federation of Civic Associations SEE Civic Associations, Federation of
- Fellowships SEE Scholarships
- Fencing SEE Sports. Fencing
- Ferries SEE ALSO Anacostia River and Flats; Potomac River
- Festival of the Arts
- Festivals (by date) SEE ALSO Music. Festivals; Theaters. American College Theater Festival; Theaters. Washington Area Theater Festival
- Festivals. Black Family Reunion
- Festivals. Cherry Blossom
- Festivals. Cherry Blossom. Pamphlets
- Festivals. DC International Film Festival
- Festivals. Folklife
- Festivals. Latin American (Latino)
- Festivals. U Street
- Fides House SEE Settlements. Fides House
- Film Collection SEE Public Library. Film Collection (499 Pennsylvania Ave.)
- Final Call SEE Newspapers. Final Call
- Finance and Revenue Department SEE ALSO Politics and Government. Chief Financial Officer
- Finance Office. 1957-1965 SEE ALSO Assessor's Office 1877-1957 (1969 became part of Finance and Revenue Dept.)
- Finances (by date) SEE ALSO Taxation
- Finances. Appropriations (by date)
- Finances. Appropriations. Legislation (by date)
- Finances. Bonds
- Finances. Budget SEE ALSO Finances. Commission on Budget and Financial Priorities (Rivlin Commission); Finances. Pamphlets. Budgets and Budget Summaries; Finances. Federal Budget Cuts (Reagan Administration); Politics and Government. Budget
- Finances. Commission on Budget and Financial Priorities (Rivlin Commission)
- Finances. Control Board SEE Finances. Financial Responsibility and Management Assistance Authority
- Finances. Cost of D.C. Government (by date)
- Finances. Debt
- Finances. Federal Budget Cuts (Reagan Administration)
- Finances. Financial Management System (FMS)
- Finances. Financial Responsibility and Management Assistance Authority (Control Board)
- Finances. Financial Responsibility and Management Assistance Authority (Control Board). Legislation
- Finances. Fiscal Relations (between DC and U.S.) (by date) SEE ALSO Federal Payment
- Finances. Fiscal Relations (between DC and U.S.). Mapes Committee
- Finances. Legislation
- Finances. Legislation SEE ALSO Finances. Pamphlets. Legislation (Hearings)(by date)
- Finances. Office of the Deputy Mayor
- Finances. Pamphlets (by date)
- Finances. Pamphlets. Budgets and Budget Summaries
- Finances. Pamphlets. General
- Finances. Pamphlets. Legislation (Hearings) (by date)
- Finances. Public Schools SEE Public Schools. Finances
- Finances. Surplus in the U.S. Treasury
- Finances. White House Plan
- Financial Authority SEE Finances. Financial Responsibility and Management Assistance Authority (Control Board)
- Financial Control Board SEE Finances. Financial Responsibility and Management Assistance Authority (Control Board)
- Financial Institutions SEE Banks
- Financial Management System (FMS) SEE Finances. Financial Management System (FMS)
- Financial Responsibility and Management Authority SEE Finances. Financial Responsibility and Management Authority (Control Board)
- Fine Arts SEE ALSO Commission of Fine Arts
- Fire Boat SEE Fire Department. Fire Boat
- Fire Department (by date)
- Fire Department. Chief
- Fire Department. Engine Houses (by date)
- Fire Department. Fire boat
- Fire Department. Legislation
- Fire Department. Prizes
- Fire Department. Salaries
- Fire Department. Speed SEE Traffic. Speed
- Fire Department. Training school
- Fire Prevention (by date)
- Fire. Legislation SEE Fire Department. Legislation
- Firefighting Museum SEE Museums. Firefighting Museum, National (proposed)
- Fires (by date)
- Fires. Famous fires (by date)
- Firewood SEE Business, Individual. Firewood
- Fireworks
- First Division SEE Memorials. First Division
- First Ward SEE Residential Sections. First Ward
- Fiscal relations SEE Finances. Fiscal relations (between DC and U.S.) (by date)
- Fish and Fishing (by date)
- Fish and Fishing. Legislation
- Fish Wharf SEE Markets. Fish Wharf
- Flag Day SEE Days, Special. Flag Day
- Flags (by date)
- Flags, D.C.
- Flies
- FLOC (For the Love Children) SEE Children's Homes. FLOC (For the Love Children)
- Floods (by date)
- Flora and Fauna SEE Fauna and Flora
- Florence Crittenton Home and Hospital SEE ALSO Children. Illegitimate
- Florists, nurseries, and landscapers SEE Business, Individual. Florists, nurseries, and landscape architects
- Flour milling SEE Business, Individual. Milling (flour)
- Flower Shows SEE Flowers. Flower Shows
- Flowers (by date)
- Flowers. Flower Shows
- Flowers. Flower Shows. Chrysanthemums
- Flowers. Flower Shows. Dahlias
- Flowers. Flower Shows. Narcissi
- Flowers. Flower Shows. Orchids SEE ALSO Societies, Clubs and Organizations. National Capital Orchid Society
- Flowers. Flower Shows. Roses SEE ALSO Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Potomac Rose Society
- Flowers. Official DC (American Beauty Rose)
- Foggy Bottom SEE Residential Sections. Foggy Bottom
- Folger Shakespeare Library (by date) SEE ALSO Theaters. Folger
- Folklife Festival SEE Festivals. Folklife
- Food (by date) SEE ALSO White House. Food; World War II. Food
- Food. Banks
- Food. Commission on Food, Nutrition and Health
- Food. Conservation
- Food. Health and Sanitation Regulations
- Food. Legislation
- Food. Prices (by date)
- Food. Stamps (by date)
- Food. Supply (by date)
- Food and Drug Administration Building (by date)
- Food delivery service SEE Business, Individual. Food delivery service
- Food preparation, commercial SEE Business, Individual. Food preparation, commercial
- Football SEE Sports. Football
- Ford's Theater Museum SEE Museums. Ford's Theater